installment4u.com.pk 2017-11-20

# Privacy Policy | i4u.com.pk

## INSTALLMENT4U (I4U) PRIVACY POLICY FOR WEBSITE

This privacy policy document contains a detailed account of how INSTALLMENT4U (I4U) uses and protects any information that you give to INSTALLMENT4U (I4U) during the use of this website (www.i4u.com.pk).  
INSTALLMENT4U (I4U) is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected and in the pursuit of this endeavour we update our security protocols regularly to comply with modern security standards. Should any information be provided by the customer upon our request for purposes of identification when using this website it is understood that any and all such information will be treated as confidential and only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.  
INSTALLMENT4U (I4U) reserves the right to make changes to this policy from time to time by if necessary. All updates will be posted by updating this page and it is hence advisable that you (the customer) check this page occasionally to ensure that you are content with any changes that have been made. This policy will be in effect as of January 1st, 2015. 

## What we collect

I4U requires the following information from the customer in order to efficiently provide the services requested by the customer:

1 - CNIC, Applicant’s Name and Applicant’s Father’s/Mother’s Name, dependents etc.  
2 - Contact information including email address, mobile and landline numbers.  
3 - Demographic information such as Area, City etc.  
4 - Other information relevant to customer assessment.  
5 - Functional information such as job title, experience, length of service, education. 

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:  

## Internal record keeping

We may use the information to evaluate your profile subject to initial approval for the product applied for.  
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.  
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for the product you have applied for or purchased from INSTALLMENT4U. We may contact you by email, phone, or mail. We may use the information provided to customize the website according to your interests. 

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over the content displayed on the other website. Therefore, we cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

## Controlling your personal information

INSTALLMENT4U (I4U) will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish for this to happen.  
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
